Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Physics, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-1997-092
  - MAP Inquiries (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - MAP Insurance 1966 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - MAP Rosenberg Foundation (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - MAP Financing (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - MAP 1965 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - MAP School Correspondence1966 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - MAP Publicity (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Publication List 1959-1972 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Abstracts 1962-1972 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Reprints, Papers, Technical Reports 1966-1972 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Technical Reports - Bardee-Tonigoe Graphs (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Technical Reports - Friar-Trefil CERN 1966 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Technical Reports - Fetter/Bell Telephone 1966 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Technical Reports - Chilton/Saperstein 1965 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Technical Reports - Goldenberg/Pratt HEPL 1963 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Technical Reports - Chilton/Argonne 1965 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Technical Reports - Nuclear Structure Conference Reprints 1964 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Technical Reports - Goldenberg/Pratt 1964 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Technical Reports - Walecka/Pratt HEPL 1962 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Technical Reports - Radha 1964 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Technical Reports - Adler/Drell SLAC 1964 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Technical Reports - Shaw/Ross UMICH 1964 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Technical Reports - Drell/Walecka SLAC 1964 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Technical Reports - Berman/Oakes SLAC 1963 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Technical Reports - Berman/Drell SLAC 1963 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Technical Reports - Berman/Tsai SLAC 1963 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Technical Reports - Lewis/Walecka HEPL 1964 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Technical Reports - Walecka HEPL 1962 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Reprints, Papers, Technical Reports 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Reprints, Contract Work 1959-1969 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Theses Drawings (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Conference Materials 1973 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Technical Reports – TN-1 through TN-24 1958-1968 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Technical Reports – TN-25 through TN-50 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Technical Reports – TN-51 through TN-59 1962 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Library Committee 1969-1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Colloquium Committee 1969-1973 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Appointment Committee 1969-1973 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Minority Affairs Committee 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Study Committee 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Admissions & Awards Committee 1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Teaching Services Committee 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Major Advisors Committee 1969 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Research Facilities Committee 1969 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Radiation Committee 1969 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Patent Policies 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Patent Committee 1973 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate Study Committee 1969-1971 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Course Permissions 1970 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Continuing Education Committee 1974-1976 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Minority Admissions 1970 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Physical Science Program 1973 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1972-1973 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1973-1974 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Professorial Group Memoranda 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Faculty & Department Memoranda 1970-1971 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Faculty & Department Memoranda 1971-1972 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Faculty & Department Memoranda 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Faculty & Department Memoranda 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Faculty & Department Memoranda 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Faculty & Department Memoranda 1875-1976 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Faculty & Department Memoranda 1976-1977 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1970-1974 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1970-1974 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Polyhronakis Administrative Correspondence 1984-1986 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Walecka Chairman Memoranda, Correspondence, Reports, etc. 1978-1981 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - American Physical Society Meeting 1949 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - American Physical Society Meeting 1966 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - American Physical Society Meeting 1966 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - American Institute of Physics Questionnaire 1969 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Federal Support for Foreign Nationals 1967 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Castle Rock Observatory (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Draft Information 1968-1970 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Education Committee 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - DoD Teach-In 6/5/1970 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Office Information (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Historical Salary Information 1968-1969 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Influenza 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Personnel Statistics 1965-1969 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Government Property Inventory 1961-1970 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Princeton Information 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - NSF Information 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Radiation Committee (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Radiation-Producing Machines (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Research Facilities Committee 1968-1970 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Safety Information 1968-1970 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Secretarial Group Meetings 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Minority Summer Program 1969 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Minority Admissions Program 1970 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Sloan Foundation Fellowship Correspondence 1967-1968 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Summer Employment (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Upward Bound Project 1964-1965 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - PSAC (President’s Science Advisory Committee) Survey 1965 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Research Administration 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Sit-Ins 1969-1970 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - SUCCEED Committee 1966-1967 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Undergraduate Office Information 1961-1970 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - United Fund Campaigns 1967-1971 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Urban League (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Department Newsletters 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Robert V. Wagner Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Van De Graaf Correspondence 1964-1968 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Schawlow Correspondence 1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Meyerhof Correspondence 1963-1968 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Little Correspondence 1965-1966 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Schiff Correspondence 1964-1968 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Ford Foundation 1967 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - White/Beaver Correspondence 1973 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Conference on Nuclear Structure 6/1963 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Feynman Films 1967 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Lebish 1969 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Packer Committee 1967 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Schwartz Conference on Advanced Placement 1969 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Conference on Science of Superconductivity 8/1969 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Varian Building Dedication 12/1962 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Science Fair - Dealtry 1966 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Secretarial Information (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Commission on College Physics Conference 2/1967 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - HEPL Research Program Proposal 1975 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Equipment Notes, Blueprints, Correspondence (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Visitors 1972-1977 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Women in Physics 1972-1977 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Varian Building 1971-1977 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Ten Year Forecast 1976-1977 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1972-1977 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Union of Research Physicists (Research Assistant Union) 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - NSF 1974-1977 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Gifts, Memorial Funds 1974-1979 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Affirmative Action 1970 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Publicity 1970 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Salary 1971-1976 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Schiff Memorial 1971 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Gardner Proposal 1974 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Black Physics Students 1970 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Meeting Minutes 1971 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Agendas 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Student Agendas 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Schiff, Bloch Memorials (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Liquefier 1975 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Black Physicists Photographs (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Miscellaneous Graphs, Reports, Notes (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Building Design Report (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Klystron Royalties, 1940-1971 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - 1-FEB-604 Observatory Fund 1978 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action 1977 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Salary Review Form 1978 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - SLAC Coordinating Committee 1978 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Grant Proposal: Little “Study of Photon” 1978 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Contracts, Grants, Class Notes, etc. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Haskin To-Dos 1975 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence 1970-1974 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Study Committee Meeting Minutes 1974 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1972-1975 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Notes 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Notes 1971-1972 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Grant Proposal: Hofstadter/Walecka “Acceleration Processes” 1977 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Haskin articles (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Grant Proposal: Cabrera/Martoff “Prototype…Bolometric” NSF 1986 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Grant Proposal: Fairbank/DeBra “Gravity Gradiometer” AFOSR 1980-1982 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Grant Proposal: Fairbank/Madey/Lockhart “Surface Shielding” AFOSR 1978-1979 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Grant Proposal: Fairbank/Lipa “Lambda Transition” NSF 1983-1986 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Grant Proposal: Fairbank/Madey “Surface Shielding” 1981-1987 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Grant Proposal: Fairbank “Quark” NSF (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Grant Proposal List 3/1989 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Grant Proposal: Van Bibber Sloan Fellowship 1987 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Grant Proposal: NASA Training, etc. 1980-1985 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Memoranda, Minutes (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Department Newsletters 1973 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - SLAC History (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Minutes, Memoranda, Correspondence, Reprints, Grants, etc. 1961-1972 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Physics at Stanford Pamphlet (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda, Minutes re: Faculty 1972 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - SURPS 1970-1972 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - NSF Funding Study 1965-1972 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Memoranda, Papers, Correspondence 1973-1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Notes 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda 1978 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Minutes 1968-1972 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - “Bloch Party” Conference 1968-1969 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Bloch Magnet 1967-1969 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Department Parties 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Professorial Group Meeting Notes 1973-1974 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Black Physics Students 1970 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Salary Review 1973 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Examinations 1962-1965 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University Sponsored Projects Report 1977 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Varian Building Contract Documents & Specifications 1961 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Memorial Lectures (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Society of Physics Students 1980-1990 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Television 1962-1964 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Slides - Observatory, Sailboats (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Audiocassettes of Lectures (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Meyerhof Reprint “Radiative Capture of Protons” 1959 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Meyerhof Travel 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Meyerhof Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Meyerhof Correspondence 1972 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Meyerhof Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Meyerhof Chairman Chronological File 1970 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Meyerhof Chairman Chronological File 1971 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Meyerhof Chairman Chronological File 1972 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Meyerhof Chairman Chronological File 1973 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Meyerhof Chairman Chronological File 1974 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Meyerhof Chairman Chronological File 1975 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Society of Physics Sigma Pi Sigma 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Summer Teaching 1976 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Teaching Assignments 1970-1977 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Telephones (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Tressider Union (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Undergraduate Physics Majors 1970-1977 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Visitors 1974-1977 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Albers Wall 1977 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - SLAC Report Material 1965-1972 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Administration 1971-1976 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Department Matters 1975-1977 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Duplication 1975 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Club 1972-1975 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Freshman Seminar (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Gift Opportunities 1975 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - HEPL 1971-1977 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Sponsored Projects, Indirect Costs 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Industrial Affiliates (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Lecture Hall Use 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - David Levine Memorial 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Applied Physics Division 1973 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - American Physical Society Meeting, Stanford University 1976 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Faculty & Staff Benefits 1973 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - B General 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous 1979 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Bunyon Lectures 1978 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Budget Cuts 1974-1975 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - ID cards 1970-1972 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Humanities & Sciences General Memoranda 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Housing 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Health Physics 1973 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Hansen Laboratory – General 1973 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - H General 1971-1973 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - C General 1977 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Conferences 1973 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Committee Assignments 1969-1973 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Course Enrollments 1971 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Graduate Studies 1971-1973 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Foreign Visitors (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Exploratorium at Varian 1976 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - K General 1971-1973 (Box 46, Folder 32)
  - M General 1972 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Grievance Procedures 1969-1971 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Students 1970-1973 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Overhead Rate 1973 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Information from Encina 1971 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Examination Schedules 1975 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Elementary Lab 1971-1972 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Curriculum Studies 1976 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Courses & Degrees 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Contracts & Grants 1975 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Department of Transportation 1972 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Textbooks 1973 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Open House 1974 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Student Advisors 1975 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Stanford University Manager 1977 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Outside Job Offers 1970-1976 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Inside Job Offers 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Job Inquiries 1974 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Department Newsletter 1970-1973 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - N General 1971-1978 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Scholarships 1972 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Salary Data 1970-1977 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - State Disability Insurance 1972-1973 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Staff Benefit Rates 1972 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Interdepartmental Correspondence 1970 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Stanford Daily Correspondence 1971 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Staff 1975 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Q General 1976 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Provost Memoranda 1972-1977 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Physics Societies 1974-1977 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Sloan Foundation 1972 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Travel 1976 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Department Miscellaneous (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Department Lectures 1972 (Box 47, Folder 34)
  - Referee Reports 1972-1976 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Reference Frame 1971-1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - R General 1972-1979 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Physics Teaching 1974-1976 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - “Physics & Man” Lecture Series 1970 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Placement Center 1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - President’s Office Memoranda 1972-1977 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Annual Picnics 1970-1978 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Meyerhof Teaching 1972-1976 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - ASSU Course Guides 1973-1977 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Meyerhof Planners 1974-1977 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Bookstore 1974 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Buckley Amendment 1976 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Budget Cuts 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Committee Assignments 1970-1977 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Conferences 1974-1977 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Continuing Education 1977 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Course Enrollment (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Dean of Humanities & Sciences 1970-1977 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Report to SU Administration on Relations between PD & SLAC 1971 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - SLAC I 12/1961-6/1963 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - SLAC II 6/1963-1970 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - SLAC 1956-1963 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - SLAC Proposal 4/1957 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous 1977-1982 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Admissions 1974-1977 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Buckley Amendment 1976 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Center for Teaching & Learning 1976 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Meyerhof Correspondence, Memoranda, etc. 1971-1976 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - ISIAC Symposium 1973 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Restricted:
    - Registrar Report 1966-1967 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Academic Standing Reports 4/1963, 4/1967, 4/1968 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Files: Glavish - Guernsey 1959-1976 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Files: Guttfreund – Hirko 1957-1974 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Personnel Files: Hinreich – Langouche 1951-1976 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Latshaw – Perl 1965-1980 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Jehl - Marriot, 1945-1968 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Files: Marshall – Schiff Jr. 1940-1970 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Pixley – Schiff 1948-1982 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Schrieffer - Serene (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: J. R. Bond; B. Couillaud; W. Fairbank (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Files: Arbarbanel – Bloom 1963-1979 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Bohr – Fearing 1963-1979 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Federman – Glavish 1963-1979 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Fairbank, W. 1960-1990 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Files: Madey, John 1976-1982 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Files: Price, John 1986 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Van Bibber, Karl 1981 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Files: Winstein, Bruce 1985-1987 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Files: Nelson 1991 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Personnel Files: Kalvius – Kohler 1955-1967 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Personnel Files: Kohn – Nordsieck 1948-1968 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Oakes – Rossing 1948-1968 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Safrata – Toller 1955-1968 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Torop – Zulliger 1946-1968 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Adams – Austin 1938-1968 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Files: Baez – Cini 1948-1968 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Cohen – Goodkind 1939-1968 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Giordmaine – Johansson 1929-1968 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Shalit – Triplett 1954-1981 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Ulrich – Zupancik 1956-1977 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Chemin, Jean Francois 1979-1982 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Donnelly, T. William 1967-1977 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Files: Abraham – Bracker 1947-1970 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Files: Braden – Friar 1948-1970 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Fried – Jew 1945-1970 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Langouche, Guid 1978 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Files: Liang, Edison 1977-1980 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Personnel Files: Freedman, Stuart 1979-1983 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Personnel Files: Junod – Liddle 1949-1969 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Personnel Files: Schmickley – Staub 1936-1969 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Personnel Files: Steele – Tweet 1940-1969 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Bound volume: cash accounts for supplies used by faculty, 1951-64 (Box 75, Folder 1)